var qlist = [  { 'question': 'Name the largest freshwater lake in the world? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Lake Superior' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Where would you find the Sea of Tranquility? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'The Moon' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is someone who shoes horses called? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'A farrier' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What item of clothing was named after its Scottish inventor? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'A Mackintosh'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What kind of weapon is a falchion? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'A sword' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which word goes before vest, beans and quartet? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'String' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is another word for lexicon? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Dictionary' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the seventh planet from the sun. ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Uranus'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who invented the rabies vaccination? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Louis Pasteur' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the worlds biggest island. ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Greenland' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is the worlds longest river? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Amazon' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the worlds largest ocean. ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Pacific'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is the diameter of Earth? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ '8,000 miles' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Where would you find the worlds most ancient forest? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Daintree Forest north of Cairns, Australia' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which four British cities have underground rail systems? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Liverpool, Glasgow, Newcastle and London' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is the capital city of Spain? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Madrid'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which country is Prague in? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Czech Republic' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which English town was a forerunner of the Parks Movement and the first city in Europe to have a street tram system? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Birkenhead' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the film noir actress who starred in I Married a Witch, The Glass Key, So Proudly We Hail! and ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Sullivans Travels. Veronica Lake' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is the oldest film ever made, and when was it made? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Roundhay Garden Scene made in 1888'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which actress has won the most Oscars? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Katharine Hepburn, with 4 Oscars and 12 nominations' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which actress said, Fasten your seatbelts. Its going to be a bumpy night, in All About Eve? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Bette Davis (as Margo Channing.)' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the director of the Lord of the Rings trilogy. ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Peter Jackson' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who played Neo in The Matrix? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Keanu Reeves'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the actress whose career began at the age of 3, and who went on to star in films such as Contact, Maverick and ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'The Silence of the Lambs? Jodie Foster' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Bray Studios, near Windsor in Berkshire, was home to which famous brand of horror films? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Hammer Horror' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In which film did Humphrey Bogart say, Well always have Paris? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Casablanca' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the world famous gardens situated ten miles outside of London, close to the River Thames. ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Kew Gardens'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which popular gardener created Barnsdale Gardens and was the author of many books such as The Ornamental Kitchen Garden, Gardeners World Practical Gardening Course and Paradise Gardens? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Geoff Hamilton' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which garden is considered to be among the Seven Wonders of the Ancient World? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'T' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What colour is a Welsh poppy? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Yellow' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What colour is a Himalayan poppy? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Blue'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the organic gardener who is almost as famous for his long blond plait as he is for his books such as Going Organic and The Gourmet Gardener and his regular appearances on the BBC radios ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Gardeners Question Time. Bob Flowerdew' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Give the alternative name for a Mountain Ash tree. ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Rowan' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which kind of bulbs were once exchanged as a form of currency? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Tulips' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'By which Latin name was Rosa Gallica previously known? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Rosa Mundi'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the only heavyweight boxing champion to finish his career of 49 fights without ever having been defeated? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Rocky Marciano' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which sport does Constantino Rocca play? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Golf' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the country where you would find the Cresta Run.',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , ' Switzerland' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'How many times was the Mens Tennis Singles at Wimbledon won by Bjorn Borg? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Five'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In 2011, which country hosted a Formula 1 race for the first time? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'India' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the game played on a lawn called a crown green. ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Bowls' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which chess piece can only move diagonally? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'A bishop' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the only footballer to have played for Liverpool, Everton, Manchester City and Manchester United. ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Peter Beardsley'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In football, who was nicknamed The Divine Ponytail? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Roberto Baggio' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In needlework, what does UFO refer to? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'An unfinished object' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the famous ballet Russian dancer who changed the face of modern ballet. ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Rudolf Nureyev' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is the painting La Gioconda more usually known as? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'The Mona Lisa'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What does the term piano mean? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'To be played softly' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the Spanish artist, sculptor and draughtsman famous for co-founding the Cubist movement. ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Pablo Picasso' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'How many valves does a trumpet have? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Three' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who painted ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'How Sir Galahad, Sir Bors, and Sir Percival were Fed with the Sanc Grael; But Sir Percivals Sister Died by the Way?'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'If you were painting with tempera, what would you be using to bind together colour pigments? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Egg yolk' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is John Leach famous for making? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Pottery' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'On what date did the Battle of Culloden take place? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , '16th April 1746' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who was Henry VIlls first wife? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Catherine of Aragon'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who became the British Prime Minister after Winston Churchill in 1955? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Sir Robert Anthony Eden, The 1st Earl of Avon' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'When did Margaret Thatcher become Prime Minister? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , '1979' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'When did the Cold War end? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , '1989' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who was the architect who designed the Millennium Dome? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Richard Rogers'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'When did the Eurostar train service between Britain and France start running? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ '14th November 1994' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'When was the euro introduced as legal currency on the world market? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , '1st January 1999' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In publishing, what does POD mean? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Print on demand' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the author of On Her Majestys Secret Service, Dr No and Thunderball, among others. ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Ian Fleming'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which Shakespeare play features Shylock? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'The Merchant of Venice' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who wrote the novel Death in Venice, which was later made into a film of the same name? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Thomas Mann' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who wrote the Vampire Chronicles, which include the novels Armand, Blood and Gold and Interview with the Vampire? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Anne Rice' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is an e-book? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'A book available in a digital, rather than printed, format'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'How tall would a double elephant folio book be? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ '50 inches' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Who wrote the contemporary childrens books about mermaids set on the coast of Cornwall? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Helen Dunmore' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'How old is the worlds oldest dictionary? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Cuneiform tablets with bilingual Sumerian-Akkadian word-lists have been dated to 2300 BC' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'On Blue Peter, what was John Noakess dog called? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Shep'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Name the BBC series about a shipping line set in Liverpool during the late 1800s. ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'The Onedin Line' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'In the TV series Dads Army, what was Captain Mainwarings first name? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'George' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What was the most watched UK TV programme of all time? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Eastenders, when Den divorced Angie, which drew 30.10 million viewers on 25th December 1986' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Which BBC music programme was broadcast weekly between 1964 and 2006? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Top of the Pops'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is sushi traditionally wrapped in? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Edible seaweed' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'May Queen, Wisley Crab, Foxwhelps and Lanes Prince Albert are all species of what? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Apples' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What is allspice alternatively known as? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Pimento' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What colour is Absynthe? ',
    'aPointer':  '3',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Green'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'What flavour is Cointreau? ',
    'aPointer':  '0',
    'answers': [ 'Orange' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'How many crocus flowers does it take to make a pound of saffron? ',
    'aPointer':  '1',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Up to 75,000 flowers, which is enough to fill an entire football pitch' , 'Random answer 3' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
  { 'question': 'Costing around $2,600 per pound and made only to order by Knipschildt, what is the name of this chocolate truffle? ',
    'aPointer':  '2',
    'answers': [ 'Random answer 1' , 'Random answer 2' , 'Chocopologie' , 'Random answer 4'  ] }, 
];
console.log( qlist );
console.log( "Qlist length = " + qlist.length );
